Terebus Volodymyr

Senior Software Development Engineer

tvolodimir@gmail.com LinkedIn (https://www.linkedin.com/in/tvolodimir)

+38(063)227-6019 Resume (http://tvolodimir.github.io/cv)

tvolodimir Projects (http://tvolodimir.github.io/projects)

Kyiv, Ukraine Github (https://github.com/tvolodimir)
27 yeas old Codepen (https://codepen.io/tvolodimir)



Back-End and Front-end Developer since 2009.

The main development platforms are .NET Framework, node.js and clients' JS for web services and mobile applications.

Programmer by education (graduated from the Faculty of Cybernetics). Likes to learn and apply new technologies and concepts, to develop interesting and unique applications and multiplayer services.

Good programming skills with plain JavaScript and his prototype paradigm. Experience with AngularJS and with developing computer games on Node.JS, websocket, canvas 2d.

SKILLS

Main: C# (4+ years), JavaScript (2+ years),

Front-End Development: HTML5, CSS3, SASS, JavaScript,

.NET APIs and frameworks: .NET Framework, WinForms, .NET Remoting, ASP.NET MVC,

ASP.NET WebApi, LINQ, MEF, WCF, WPF, ASP.NET, Silverlight, XNA, ADO.NET, EF, DLR,

Parallel Extensions,

JavasScript / Node.JS APIs and frameworks: JavaScript (plaint, prototype), node.js, Grunt, AngularJS, Express, Connect, socket.io, Canvas 2D API, CSS 3D Transforms, Web Audio API, File API, IndexedDB,

Source control: SVN, GIT,

Deployment: ClickOnce Windows Installer,

Database tools and languages: MSSQL, Microsoft Access, MongoDB,

Languages and compilers: C#, JavaScript, T-SQL, XAML,

Development tools: Visual Studio, WebStorm, Expression Blend, Expression Web, WebMatrix,

SQL Server Management Studio,

Software engineering: OOP, Software design pattern, Event-driven programming, Functional programming,

WORK EXPERIENCE

Digicode (http://digicode.net) Ukraine, Kyiv C#/JavaScript Developer Sep 2012 - Present

Developing e-gambling solutions on the platforms: .NET, HTML, using the latest technologies of HTML5, CSS3, Asp.Net WebApi, Entity Framework.

Navativo (RIKODI) — social service for creating, sharing and collaborating memorable events and any stories by adding audio, videos, photos, digitized articles, and links to outside web stories. (It's complicated client-server web project with ASP.NET, MSSQL, AngularJS, I have roles of architect and principal developer) http://web.navativo.digicode.ua/ (4 months development.). (ASP.NET Web Api, SiqnalR, MSSQL, AngularJS, Social integrations, Multimedia Storage/Processing)

Dominos Pizza Delivery Monitoring — Real-time monitoring web-service for managing couriers. (Client-server system on multitenant architecture with ASP.NET Web Api, SiqnalR, MSSQL, AngularJS, I have roles of architect and principal developer) (2 months development.) (2 months development.). (ASP.NET Web Api, SiqnalR, MSSQL, AngularJS)



Vega — engagement software for charities and fundraisers. (Client-server system on multitenant architecture with ASP.NET WebForm, MSSQL, I have role of C# developer) http://www.vega.works/ (4 months development.). (ASP.NET WebForm, MSSQL)

888 European Roulette — set of mobile games for gambling of 888 Holdings. (Html-based mobile game using HTML Canvas 2D Context, CSS transforms, CSS Animations, HTML Audio Element, Web Audio API. My responsibilities was designing and develop game core and optimize render performance.) https://mc-888games.safe-iplay.com/#European%20Roulette (4 months development.). (HTML Canvas 2D Context, CSS transforms, CSS Animations, HTML Audio Element, Web Audio API, Grunt)

All Slots/All Jackpot Casino — online casino groups. My responsibilities was wrapping and publishong existing web-based casinos lobby with games to iOS native applications with adding pushing services and deep analytic servies. (ObjectiveC, iOS, Html)

LPS — SEO management system. (MSSQL, Drupal, .NET)

Ziccu — German project of e-gambling. Web/TV-based online gambling. (Muti-tiers system with MSSQL, .NET and Drupal platforms used Entity Framework, WCF, ASP.NET WebApi, MSSQL, Drupal, Memcached. My responsibilities was develop and support back-end part of .NET servises infrastructure and MSQL) (6 months development.) (Entity Framework, WCF, ASP.NET WebApi, MSSQL, Drupal, Memcached, T-SQL)

Jackpot SlotGame — web-game for gambling of Ziccu. (My responsibilities was designing and develop browser slot-game with using CSS transforms, CSS Animations, Html Audio Element) (CSS transforms, CSS Animations, Html Audio Element)

UMG (http://umg.com.ua) Ukraine, Kyiv C# Developer Sep 2010 - Sep 2012

Developing and supporting applications for marketing research.

Fora – software for processing large amounts of data for statistical analysis and transformation of the structure with the ability to use macros and support for all statistical models in marketing. (C#, WinForms, .Net Remoting)

Softphone for CATI — client software for call center operators. (C#, WinForms, SIP)

Licensing Service — service of licensing and administration software. (C#, WinForms, .Net Remoting, IL)

Fora Office Add-ins — component integration between MS Office products and software «Fora» . (C#, .Net Remoting, MS Office)

Athena Quest — software for creation questionnaires of any level of complexity for respondents in both electronic and printed form. (C#, WinForms, HTML, CSS, JS)

CATI — multicomponent system for implementation, processing, storage, and data collection; service for filling and processing questionnaires. service call center for survey respondents on VoIP; service to administer projects. (C#, WinForms, ASP.Net, HTML, JavaScript)

Anketarium — administration system for logic and staff control, data processing of execution of works. (C#, WinForms)

Open source, Hobbies, Curriculum, C4F

I fascinated in coding different fun programs which touches with computer graphics, computer algorithms, geometry, mathematics, physics. My favorites languages and technologies are C#, JavaScript, OpenGI, XNA, Silverlight, CSS3, WebGL, HTML Canvas 2D, Web Audio API. Most of my latest codings oriented for web- and mobile-oriented platforms using the technologies of HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Node.js, .NET. Other latest projects: Projects (http://tvolodimir.github.io/demos)

Balls game — real-time multiplayer html 2d game used one authorized server and own physics engine. (HTML5, HTML Canvas 2D, WebSocket, node.js)

Einstaine Puzzle game — html game. It's modification of classic Einstaine puzzle. Most complicated features were algorithms of generation and solving generic Einstaine puzzle game and full CSS Transform 3D supports. (HTML5, CSS Transform 3D, HTML Canvas 2D)

Fast Multipole Method of N-Body simulation — application that visualizes the problem of n-bodies by fastest algorithm Fast Multipole Method. (C#, Silverlight, "Fast Multipole Method" Algorithms)

3d Scene Viewer — software application for creating and editing scenes of dimensional graphics and animation. (WinForms, C#, OpenGL)

Sky Scattering — implementation of sky scattering model and its application in Computer graphics. (C#, XNA)

EDUCATION

- Taras Shevchenko National University of Kyiv , Faculty of Cybernetics, Master of Science in Applied Mathematics, 2004 - 2010
- Physics and Mathematics lyceum (UPML) of Taras Shevchenko Kyiv University, 2001 2004

LANGUAGES

- · Ukraine native
- English upper intermediate

PERSONAL QUALITIES & INTERESTS

- Mathematics, physics, programming, photography, drawing and computer graphics, backpacking, geotourism, hiking, canoe camping, skiing, camping
- · Accurate, responsible, erudite, have analytical and creative thinking
- · Willingly learns new technologies and concepts
- · Has no bad habits

Resume last modification: 24 February 2015